Ankur Banga

nkrbanga80@gmail.com +91- 8469414913 C-601, Panchshlok Homes, Chandkheda Ahmedabad, Gujarat

Summary

Ankur is an experienced corporate travel professional with 8 years of experience in managing corporate travel program efficiently and saving significant travel cost through the diverse knowledge of travel industry.

Skills

- · Concur Travel booking tool
- · Travel Coordination
- Vendor Management
- Travel Savings
- Jira Service Desk

- · Travel Arrangements
- · Event Management
- Travel Spend Reports/MIS
- Microsoft office
- · Travel Cost Optimization

Experience

Travel Specialist

Sophos Technologies Pvt. Ltd. • Ahmedabad, Gujarat

02/2019 - Present

- End to end management of Self booking tool SAP Concur travel booking tool.
- Queries handling related to concur tool, booking help to employees Air fare & hotel search on Self booking tool.
- Managing Global Business Travel for the company employees and Visa processing for different countries Like — USA, UK, Middle East, South East Asia, Africa etc.
- Event Management -Successfully Managed Annual Events like Company Kick off, APJ Sales Summit — Bali, Indonesia, and other small events - team outings etc.
- Managing Travel Vendors, Travel Cost Savings Travel Cost Analysis reports/MIS for each Business Function on monthlybasis.
- Continuously improving the travel Management process & Ad hoc Admin responsibilities Event/Conference Management for company requirement.

Assistant Manager - Travel Desk

Ecofrost Technologies Pvt. Ltd. • Pune, Maharashtra

08/2018 - 02/2019

- Implementation of online/self-travel booking tool for company employee
- Managing Overall Business Travel for the company employees.
- Air ticketing, Hotel Booking, Cab Booking, Event Management. Managing
- Travel Vendors, Travel Cost Saving & managing Travel MIS.

Sr. Travel and Hospitality Executive

Sterlite Technologies Ltd. • Ahmedabad, Gujarat

02/2017 - 06/2018

- Managing efficient Business Travel for entire organization including Flights, Train, Bus tickets, Hotel booking Car Rentals, Cab Booking.
- Managing office events, meeting rooms, conferences. Issuing Travel Advance/ Foreign currency for employees prior to travel date.
- Travel & Expense Reporting Creating and Maintaining Reports of Travel expense of the company.

Travel Desk Executive

Motif India Infotech Pvt. Ltd. • Ahmedabad, Gujarat

04/2016 - 02/2017

- Personal Assistant to CEO Assisting the CEO of the company for Travel Booking, Calendar Management and Scheduling Meeting with Clients etc
- . Travel & Expense Reporting Creating and Maintaining Reports of Travel expense of the company.

Travel Executive 08/2012 - 05/2016

Collabera Technologies Pvt. Ltd. • Vadodara, Gujarat

- Corporate Travel Management Arranging Efficient Travel for Company employees, Clients, Consultants Booking Flights, Hotels, Car Rentals, Cabs.
- Travel & Expense Reporting Creating and Maintaining Various Reports of Travel expenses and details on Monthly and weekly Basis.

Education

BBA (Honours) - Tourism & Travel Management

Sadar Patel University • Anand, Gujarat

05/2012

 $Graduated in BBA \, hons. \, with 74\% \, (Distinction).$

Languages

• English • Hindi